AmirHossein Farnaghizad

Biotechnology Student

Tehrān

amirfarnzad@yahoo.com

+989102330636

I am an undergraduate Biotechnology student at Islamic Azad University with internship experience at the Pasteur Institute of Iran. Equipped with strong skills in leadership, communication, marketing, and biotechnology knowledge, currently focused on academic pursuits.

Work Experience

Academic Advisor

National Organization for Development of Exceptional Talents - Tehrān February 2022 to May 2022

Research Intern

Pasteur institute of Iran - Tehrān April 2022 to April 2022

Education

Bachelor of Science in Biotechnology

Islamic Azad University - Tehrān September 2021 to Present

High school diploma

National Organization for Development of Exceptional Talents - Tehran

Skills

- · Creative Writing
- Leadership
- Teaching
- · Communication Skills
- Marketing
- Biotechnology

Languages

- English Expert
- Farsi Fluent

Links

http://amir.int-n.info

https://github.com/amirfarnzad

https://linkedin.com/in/amirfarnzad

Certifications and Licenses

Industrial Biotechnology

September 2023 to Present

 $https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/verify/MYBE9RMZ2ZTV?trk = public_profile_seecredential$